# VIACHESLAV YERMOKHIN

# Software Engineer | Algo Trading Developer

### **SUMMARY**

I'm a Software Developer with a vast array of knowledge in Web development languages and Algo trading experience, Databases.

My object is simply to be the best web developer that I can be and contribute to the technology industry with all that I know and can do.

- Knows HTML and javascript Frameworks, tailwindCSS and MUI components
- Eye-catching UI/UX design for web sites
- Build Algo trading strategy with MT4/5 and Tradingview
- High communication skills for technical context in English

### **EXPERIENCE**

### Web Developer

03/2023 - 10/2023

### **Creative Marketing Nerds**

Odessa, Ukraine

- Created 10+ websites on different platforms
- eCommerce website
- Woo-commerce Dropshipping
- **Shopify Premium Websites**

# Fontend Developer | Shopify Developer

08/2021 - 03/2023

Luxoft

Odessa, Ukraine

- Developed and maintain a high-quality, scalable Shopify store for the client
- Collaborate with client to understand their business needs and goals, and provide recommendations on store design and functionality
- Developed scalable applications using the MEAN stack and created POCs for rest service development using Node.js, Express.js, and MongoDB
- Implemented custom features and functionality using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Liquid, and Shopify APIs
- Ensured stores are optimized for SEO and implemented CRO best practices
- Extend Shopify's functionalities to the next level using storefront APIs and meta fields

# Frontend Developer & Web Designer

05/2020 - 07/2021

#### Capgemini Engineering

Odessa, Ukraine

- Started my career and gained a lot of expertise in the field of Web-development. Created 100+ websites on different platforms
- Redesigned 10+ websites and logos by using Adobe Photoshop, Flash and
- Developed and launched 2 e-commerce platform and related products online
- Increased mobile orders by 18% by developing a mobile application for ordering and payment
- Gained experience with various web development tools including Bower, NPM, Git, Material design, Gulp, and cloud services like AWS, Azure, GCP, Heroku, and

### **EDUCATION**

**Bachelor of Computer Application** 

2016 - 2020

Odessa National Polytechnic University

Odessa, Ukraine

### **SKILLS**

C++ · MetaTrader4 · MetaTrader5 ·

Bot Development · MQL5 ·

Trading Automation · Web Design ·

React · WordPress · Shopify ·

Plugin Development · Webflow ·

HTML · CSS · javascript · python

## LANGUAGES

Ukrainian Native English **Proficient** Japanese Advanced

